<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--======Hey bro, I'm leaving this note to remind you of two things: the English here is all machine translated, and there's maybe a hundred thousand words here, so good luck to you. Also, the Chinese translation file is accurate, but there are tens of thousands of characters there too : (======-->
<Defs>
	
	<!-- <Shooting></Shooting>
			<Melee></Melee>
			<Construction></Construction>
			<Mining></Mining>
			<Cooking></Cooking>
			<Plants></Plants>
			<Animals></Animals>
			<Crafting></Crafting>
			<Artistic></Artistic>
			<Medicine></Medicine>
			<Social></Social>
			<Intellectual></Intellectual> -->
	<!--============================== 太空 Space 5-25没校对============================-->
	
	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space01</defName>
		<title>celestia traveller</title>
		<titleShort>traveller</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] has an interplanetary shuttle of [PAWN_possessive] own, with which [PAWN_pronoun] pursues the life of [PAWN_possessive] dreams - the freedom to travel freely from planet to planet in [PAWN_possessive] home galaxy, pioneering, admiring, and documenting the magnificent wonders of the uncharted landscapes as [PAWN_pronoun] pleases. \n\nThe only downside to such a free life is that [PAWN_pronoun] can only obtain hobo level rations and benefits, which leaves [PAWN_pronoun] with the occasional odd job to maintain [PAWN_possessive] standard of living.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>3</Artistic>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Plants>1</Plants>
			<Mining>-1</Mining>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>
	
	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space02</defName>
		<title>celestia photography blogger</title>
		<titleShort>blogger</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] started out simply being amazed by the sights of space and planets, and occasionally posted holograms of the sights [PAWN_pronoun] saw during [PAWN_possessive] travels on social media platforms. But [PAWN_pronoun] soon found that many people who couldn't travel in person found solace in [PAWN_possessive]'s holograms, and this attention brought [PAWN_pronoun] prestige and motivation to continue doing what [PAWN_pronoun] was doing - both mentally and materially. So one day, [PAWN_nameDef] quit [PAWN_possessive] old job and turned to social networking to make a splash with space holograms.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>6</Artistic>
			<Social>2</Social>
			<Crafting>-1</Crafting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>
	
	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space03</defName>
		<title>celestia space station bartender</title>
		<titleShort>bartender</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] working as a bartender on a regular space station on the main route that's kind of like an old-timey high-speed service area, except it's in space. \n\n[PAWN_nameDef] serves drinks to those who come here, letting the liquids wash away tired bodies and souls, it's [PAWN_possessive] job that really makes this space station a safe haven. But more people would just choose to go to the kiosk on the side for a cheap drink is all.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>6</Social>
			<Cooking>2</Cooking>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>
	
	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space04</defName>
		<title>celestia docking port engineer</title>
		<titleShort>port engineer</titleShort>
		<description>Most of the repetitive and monotonous tasks in Celestia society had been left entirely to robots, and naturally that included docking, maintenance, and fuelling of ships at the space station.\n\n Aside from the living members of the station's security department, [PAWN_nameDef] is pretty much the only organic staff member at the docking port, and [PAWN_possessive] job for the most part is to simply monitor the workings of the station's docking port for proper functioning from a comfortable room, and then spend the rest of [PAWN_possessive] time away from all social interaction and living beings to concentrate on relaxing. Some would blame the [PAWN_possessive] job for being too easy, but the truth was that no one wanted the [PAWN_pronoun] to suddenly get busy, as that often meant that the docking port had experienced a major malfunction in the automated systems that could not be undone.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>4</Crafting>
			<Construction>2</Construction>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space05</defName>
		<title>celestia station police</title>
		<titleShort>police</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as a police officer at an ordinary space habitation station in Celestia's Inner Rim domain, where [PAWN_pronoun] and [PAWN_possessive] colleagues are responsible for policing an area. [PAWN_pronoun] has undergone a series of specialised training in criminal investigation, combat, non-lethal shooting, and good expression management. \n\nBut [PAWN_possessive] these skills were not put into practice a few times, not because of incompetence, but because of the good social environment. More often than not, [PAWN_pronoun] have had to mediate the whimsical conflicts of community residents.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>4</Social>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Melee>1</Melee>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space06</defName>
		<title>celestia station police</title>
		<titleShort>police</titleShort>
		<description>Graduating from the police academy with honours, [PAWN_nameDef] went to work as a police officer at a Celestia habitation station located in the Outer Rim realm with a lot of enthusiasm. \n\nPolicing here tends to be less peaceful than at Celestia's habitation station in the Inner Rim, with shootings and gang problems still present in the huge habitation station. After the initial rustiness and adjustment, [PAWN_pronoun] began to learn many of the ways to survive in this environment and had to use some violence to solve problems.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>4</Shooting>
			<Melee>3</Melee>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Social>1</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space07</defName>
		<title>celestia fighting instructor</title>
		<titleShort>fight-instructor</titleShort>
		<description>Almost all Celestia has had a little bit of combat training at one time or another, and [PAWN_nameDef] is extraordinarily adept at it. [PAWN_pronoun] had a special interest in this primal adrenaline-rising sensation, which guided [PAWN_pronoun] to eventually become a good fighting instructor, training the equally good Celestia youths in anthropomorphic combat. \n\nBut the fights wrapped in full virtual reality and force feedback equipment made [PAWN_pronoun] feel that something was missing - there was no splattering of blood and long-lasting pain, not to mention the threat of life. [PAWN_pronoun] had always longed for a real fight, a fight for his life.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Melee>5</Melee>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Social>1</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space08</defName>
		<title>celestia security leader</title>
		<titleShort>security</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] Provides security for clients with special needs, and while that need has become infrequent, every order is almost always big business. Whether it was a researcher looking for dead frontiers to collect bug samples or a sociologist bored of delving into the Outer Rim, they always had a need for security. \n\nWhile more often than not, it was just certain famous figures who needed [PAWN_pronoun] and [PAWN_possessive] colleagues to help keep order, when force was needed to solve a problem, [PAWN_pronoun] hardly ever let its customers down either.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>4</Shooting>
			<Melee>3</Melee>
			<Social>2</Social>
			<Crafting>-3</Crafting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space09</defName>
		<title>celestia security leader</title>
		<titleShort>security</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] provides security for one of the docking ports, and under the watchful eye of strong security robots, the already law-abiding Celestia don't commit much of anything most of the time. [PAWN_pronoun]'s job, more often than not, is to mediate conflicts, prevent drunken Abyssaltia from going crazy, stop modified creatures from escaping from one of the institutes, and take on the occasional accidental evacuation.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>4</Social>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Animals>-1</Animals>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space10</defName>
		<title>celestia construction supervisor</title>
		<titleShort>supervisor</titleShort>
		<description>Most of Celestia's buildings are automatically programmed to be constructed, and some are even simply moulded in one piece with engineered nanomachines. [PAWN_nameDef]'s job, on the other hand, was to oversee the engineering projects that still required mechanical construction, to avoid the unhinged robots from doing anything stupid. Like building a wall and shutting itself down until it ran out of power and shut down, or tearing down some unstable support structure and driving itself into a raw stake. \n\n In his spare time, [PAWN_pronoun] occasionally leaves some of his artistic inspiration in these engineering projects.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Construction>5</Construction>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Crafting>3</Crafting>
			<Plants>-1</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space11</defName>
		<title>celestia station engineer</title>
		<titleShort>station engineer</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves on Celestia's Academy of Engineering Sciences, providing designs for the skeletal structures of Celestia's space habitation stations. Habitat stations that sit atop infinite voids, meltable ice, fragile rock formations, and moving fluids are but frail specks among the stars, and it is [PAWN_pronoun]'s job to make them reliable. \The ever-expanding population of Celestia prompted [PAWN_pronoun] and [PAWN_possessive] colleagues to also keep travelling to more and more places once considered unsuitable for the construction of habitation stations. It was architects like [PAWN_nameDef] who continued to open up new frontiers for Celestia before the critical breakthrough in planetary transformation.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Mining>6</Mining>
			<Construction>4</Construction>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Social>-3</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space12</defName>
		<title>celestia art-loving engineer</title>
		<titleShort>art-loving engineer</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] works for the Celestia Academy of Engineering Sciences, where he is responsible for designing the skeletal structure of the Celestia Space Habitat Station in order to expand Celestia's living space. Beyond the tedious mathematical calculations and mechanical analyses of the station's skeleton, [PAWN_pronoun] occasionally adds his own aesthetically pleasing whims to the design. [PAWN_pronoun] has always believed that art and beauty are an integral part of people's lives. \n\nThese beautiful inspirations, together with the sense of mission to open up new frontiers, have become the driving force behind [PAWN_pronoun]'s work.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Construction>4</Construction>
			<Artistic>4</Artistic>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Cooking>-3</Cooking>
			<Social>-2</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space13</defName>
		<title>celestia mantle engineer</title>
		<titleShort>mantle engineer</titleShort>
		<description>Those magnificent clusters of subterranean habitation stations built on solid geological structures that reach into the earth's mantle have a graphic common name: ‘underground cities’. \n\nAnd [PAWN_nameDef] is a veteran engineer who is adept at designing and building underground city structures - digging thousands of metres deep into the earth, expanding the magnificent underground space that is comparable to the size of a continent, laying out the tall pillars that support the dome, and finally, projecting the azure blue sky of the mother planet on the top of the dome. Asteroid impacts, structural deterioration, accidents, natural and man-made disasters are all problems that [PAWN_pronoun] needs to take into account, and [PAWN_possessive] knowledge is fundamental for [PAWN_pronoun] to have the means to solve them at all times.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Mining>7</Mining>
			<Construction>5</Construction>
			<Medicine>-4</Medicine>
			<Social>-3</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space14</defName>
		<title>celestia structural artist</title>
		<titleShort>artist</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is good at designing art that embellishes people's lives. Celestia never refuses artistic expression, and the cramped space habitat needs to be embellished to inspire people. The [PAWN_pronoun]is good at designing distinctive art forms for different occasions, either in relief or painted, and the use of nanomachines can turn [PAWN_possessive]thoughts into reality. On the domes, skeletons, pillars, and all corners of the station, [PAWN_pronoun] uses his art to decorate everyone's emotions.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>6</Artistic>
			<Construction>4</Construction>
			<Crafting>2</Crafting>
			<Social>-3</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space15</defName>
		<title>celestia deep-space shipbreaker</title>
		<titleShort>shipbreaker</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] works as a shipbreaker on a huge recycling ship. The job was somewhat like scavenging, there was always the occasional unlucky ship left in the universe forever, becoming space junk, and it was [PAWN_possessive] duty to turn that junk into treasure. \n\nWhen the bodies and dog tags are matched and put into the morgue, and all the processes are confirmed, [PAWN_nameDef] can take the laser cutter and demolition explosives, and in the corridor of the spaceship, which is even more complicated than a mine tunnel, start to cut off the valuable parts with the drones little by little, and then dismantle the rest of the carbon nanomaterials and alloy constructions into small, easy-to-handle pieces. After much dismantling, it was more or less touch and go, and when asked, [PAWN_nameDef] would always say that [PAWN_pronoun] knew a little something about building spaceships as well.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Mining>8</Mining>
			<Construction>4</Construction>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Social>-4</Social>
			<Medicine>-2</Medicine>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space16</defName>
		<title>celestia deep miner</title>
		<titleShort>miner</titleShort>
		<description>The mining work of [PAWN_nameDef] is different from that of the ordinary miner, [PAWN_pronoun] has to pilot a special ship into the deepest parts of the asteroids and dwarf planets, drilling into the active or cooled mantles of the rocky planets, penetrating into the high-pressure, liquid sea of metallic hydrogen of the giant planets, and diving into the liquid ocean of diamonds of the far-sunny planets, to harvest the deepest layers of minerals which have already formed a special crystalline structure. The deepest minerals that have formed a special crystal structure. \n\n[PAWN_possessive] mental faculties have been tested by long periods of claustrophobia, and [PAWN_possessive] ore-excavation techniques are second to none - though not all of them are interoperable with the unusual miner.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Mining>8</Mining>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Shooting>1</Shooting>
			<Animals>-4</Animals>
			<Social>-3</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space17</defName>
		<title>celestia space miner</title>
		<titleShort>miner</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] went deep into space to mine the water ice and metals hidden between the rocky silica that was the lifeblood of Celestia's civilisation, and [PAWN_pronoun] was an ordinary cell in that living stream of blood, of which the intelligence of a human being was an irreplaceable part. \n\n During the long voyage back and forth through the asteroid belt, [PAWN_pronoun] passed the time as best he could, and one of the choices was to amuse his pets - there was more than enough redundancy in the life-support systems to support more than just one pet anyway.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Mining>5</Mining>
			<Animals>3</Animals>
			<Plants>2</Plants>
			<Social>-3</Social>
			<Artistic>-2</Artistic>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space18</defName>
		<title>celestia asteroid artist</title>
		<titleShort>artist</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is experimenting with a very new form of art: cutting off a chunk of an asteroid in space, then using a laser rifle to carve out the sculpture a little bit, and finally dropping the sculpture off somewhere for display as performance art. \n\nNo one knows how [PAWN_pronoun] came up with this kind of thing, or how [PAWN_pronoun] suddenly caught fire on interstellar social media platforms, but everyone has to admit that [PAWN_pronoun] does have that kind of skill.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>5</Artistic>
			<Shooting>4</Shooting>
			<Mining>3</Mining>
			<Medicine>-4</Medicine>
			<Social>-2</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space19</defName>
		<title>celestia onboard chef</title>
		<titleShort>chef</titleShort>
		<description>Even in the midst of sprawling deep space, eating is an integral part of life. On a ship where all living materials are incredibly scarce, [PAWN_nameDef] is adept at utilising a handful of ingredients and seasonings to satisfy the crew's taste buds while avoiding circulatory system contamination to the greatest extent possible. \n\nOne of the foods that [PAWN_pronoun] is most adept at cooking is soybeans - all it takes is a few minerals, or a fermentation tank, and [PAWN_pronoun] can make fancy food while being self-sufficient, making the crew's meals countless times richer than they would have been if they had just eaten nutrient paste! . And when the crew grew tired of the taste, [PAWN_pronoun] could bring out [PAWN_pronoun]'s second best food for cooking: potatoes.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Cooking>7</Cooking>
			<Plants>3</Plants>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Social>-3</Social>
			<Animals>-3</Animals>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space20</defName>
		<title>celestia alien-eating gourmet</title>
		<titleShort>gourmet</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] was definitely not the first to eat crabs, but [PAWN_pronoun] is indeed one of the few to eat alien creatures. On Celestia's home planet, there are still many unverified alien species, and those that are confirmed to be non-toxic or mildly toxic, and suitable enough to be served on the table, [PAWN_pronoun] dares to boldly experiment with their flavours. Sometimes it ends with vomiting and diarrhoea, and sometimes with a whole new undiscovered delicious taste. If possible, [PAWN_nameDef] would like to write a cookbook about his experiences someday. \n\nIn [PAWN_pronoun]'s career, gifts have been rare, but [PAWN_pronoun] did discover one - fried breadcrumb-coated ice-insectjelly-cream.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Cooking>6</Cooking>
			<Medicine>4</Medicine>
			<Animals>2</Animals>
			<Social>-5</Social>
			<Construction>-3</Construction>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space21</defName>
		<title>celestia greenhouse administrator</title>
		<titleShort>greenhouse manager</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] manages a patch of agricultural greenhouses in the habitation station, where countless vibrant genetically-modified crops and the dead silence of space are often separated only by a thin layer of steel plate, and even though there are countless mechanical monitors and an artificial intelligence is always analysing the environment, the simple artificial ecology is still incredibly fragile, and it often takes only the lack of a single substance, a single pathogen infection, to destroy the rations that sustain tens of thousands of people. \n\nAnd it was [PAWN_nameDef]‘s task to maintain the fragile balance in the greenhouse, to nip the disaster in the bud with [PAWN_pronoun]’s expert knowledge of agriculture - of course, picking a little bit of edible portion now and then and bringing it back to eat certainly wasn't a disruption of the balance.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Plants>8</Plants>
			<Medicine>3</Medicine>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Social>-4</Social>
			<Mining>-2</Mining>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space22</defName>
		<title>celestia agri-view block administrator</title>
		<titleShort>block administrator</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is responsible for the management of an agriculturally landscaped, self-sustaining artificial ecological block known as the Agri-View block. This highly genetically modified ecosystem is immensely stable and requires little maintenance other than necessary observation and data logging, which allows [PAWN_pronoun] to take on a job more akin to that of a primitive forest keeper than that of an agricultural greenhouse keeper. \n\n[PAWN_pronoun] had all but no need to worry about the risk of failure in this block, and although even if the miniature artificial star or the cyclic maintenance system did fail in that one-in-ten-thousand probability [PAWN_pronoun] couldn't do much to help, [PAWN_pronoun] had still received the necessary training to patrol and maintain this ‘forest’ to keep the oxygen and water circulating throughout the station, and to ensure that Celestia living in space will still be able to walk through the forest tomorrow with the sound of water echoing and real birdsong.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Plants>5</Plants>
			<Artistic>4</Artistic>
			<Social>2</Social>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space23</defName>
		<title>celestia public-upbringing-centres worker</title>
		<titleShort>caretaker</titleShort>
		<description>In Celestia's society, the concept of ‘gender’ has become as much a character label as ‘bold,’ ‘delicate,’ and ‘emotional’ have become the same character labels. The concept of ‘child’ has become a temporal and spatial continuation of the common idea of plural individuals, rather than a short-sighted need and tool for collective material survival. [PAWN_nameDef] The work of the public institution is to raise these children in a centralised nurturing environment, to shape their personality and social relationships through action in the context of food, clothing and shelter, and to make them aware of their spontaneous values and directions through thought. And in this, the public fosters never refuse the personal participation of the blood relatives of these children. This makes [PAWN_nameDef] less like nannies or teachers and more like gardeners of the soul.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>6</Social>
			<Medicine>4</Medicine>
			<Animals>2</Animals>
			<Mining>-5</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space24</defName>
		<title>celestia career-planning evaluator</title>
		<titleShort>career evaluator</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is good at reading people, and especially at detecting in the myriad of minute details how to achieve [PAWN_pronoun]'s desired ends. From people's meticulous career files and short interview questions and answers, [PAWN_pronoun] evaluates and advises on their life-long career plans. PAWN_pronoun does not force anyone into a particular career, and these assessments are never recorded on paper. [PAWN_pronoun] is just advice, full of [PAWN_pronoun]'s sincerest expectations, and [PAWN_pronoun] hopes that everyone can realise their values. Celestia hopes that everyone can realise their values.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>7</Social>
			<Intellectual>5</Intellectual>
			<Construction>-4</Construction>
			<Plants>-3</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space25</defName>
		<title>celestia ecologist</title>
		<titleShort>ecologist</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] works at Celestia's Academy of Ecological Sciences, alongside Celestia's creators, the Abyssaltia, using Celestia's advanced artificial ecological technology to study and protect the rare ecosystems of their home planet. The ‘Bright Blue Dot’, over 95% of which is covered by the ocean, has been gradually unbalanced by deep-sea industrial development, and its fragile deep-sea ecosystems are collapsing due to sunlight, ocean currents, and physical and chemical imbalances such as temperature, salinity, pressure, and density. Before the planet's ecological resources and evolutionary footprint are completely lost, [PAWN_pronoun] has an obligation to reconstruct artificial ecosystems to protect these natural creations.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Plants>6</Plants>
			<Intellectual>4</Intellectual>
			<Medicine>3</Medicine>
			<Mining>-5</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space26</defName>
		<title>celestia archivist</title>
		<titleShort>archivist</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] works at Celestia's Academy of Historical Research. [PAWN_pronoun] is determined to uncover all histories, documenting every human story from the known to the unknown. [PAWN_pronoun] records major events in Celestia's history, seeking historical facts from those living fossils, the Abyssia. But more often, [PAWN_pronoun] spends entire weeks immersed in the archives, attempting to reconstruct history from fragmented relics, piecing together the evolution and development of human civilization over millennia. Exploring the truths of history, illuminating the path for Celestia.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Intellectual>6</Intellectual>
			<Social>3</Social>
			<Artistic>2</Artistic>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space27</defName>
		<title>celestia beacon technician</title>
		<titleShort>beacontender</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is one of the best technicians at Celestia Technical Institute. Using automated machinery, [PAWN_pronoun] alone can maintain all navigation beacons around an entire habitation station. [PAWN_possessive] work provides guidance for passing vessels, preventing them from getting lost in the endless void. Off-duty, [PAWN_pronoun] just wants to lie in [PAWN_possessive] single dormitory, snacking and watching holographic channels.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>6</Crafting>
			<Construction>4</Construction>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Social>-5</Social>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space28</defName>
		<title>celestia navigator</title>
		<titleShort>navigator</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] analyzes stellar cartography data from computers to design and guide optimal flight routes for spacecraft. [PAWN_pronoun] is not permanently assigned to any single vessel, as [PAWN_possessive] employers sometimes require high-speed arrivals, sometimes fuel conservation, and occasionally a balance of both. Even when clients need [PAWN_pronoun] to obscure ship radar signatures and breach no-fly zones past patrols, [PAWN_pronoun] can professionally calculate the optimal trajectory with maximum efficiency.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Intellectual>7</Intellectual>
			<Social>4</Social>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Mining>-5</Mining>
			<Plants>-3</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space29</defName>
		<title>celestia starship engineer</title>
		<titleShort>starship-engineer</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] has participated in the design of various spacecraft models. [PAWN_possessive] designs are always utility-oriented, and to achieve the intended purposes, [PAWN_pronoun] often personally designs the ship's AI systems and electromechanical systems. The easily maintainable yet highly customizable structures combined with excellent spacecraft performance have earned [PAWN_pronoun] some renown in the industry.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>5</Crafting>
			<Construction>4</Construction>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Social>-3</Social>
			<Plants>-2</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space30</defName>
		<title>celestia shipboard physician</title>
		<titleShort>ship-doctor</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as a physician aboard a spacecraft, safeguarding the crew's physical and mental health. Traveling between the Inner and Outer Rim domains, the lonely journeys spanning dozens of astronomical units not only exert immense psychological pressure on the crew but also expose them to unstable gravity and radiation, creating a vicious cycle that disrupts everyone's condition. [PAWN_nameDef] must maintain [PAWN_possessive] own stability, pulling both crewmembers and the entire ship back from the self-destructive vortex of the void through regular checkups and psychological counseling.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Medicine>7</Medicine>
			<Social>3</Social>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space31</defName>
		<title>celestia exotic veterinarian</title>
		<titleShort>pet-doctor</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a seasoned veterinarian who always knows how to calm down and treat various bizarre little pets - yes, bizarre, as Celestia's gene-editing technology has made pet species and purposes extraordinarily peculiar. Though their bodily structures differ, the biological systems revealed under X-rays and AI analysis always betray the consistency of biological origins, which forms the basis of [PAWN_pronoun] treatment for these creatures.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Animals>6</Animals>
			<Medicine>4</Medicine>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
			<Mining>-3</Mining>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space32</defName>
		<title>celestia cyber beastmaster</title>
		<titleShort>cyber-tamer</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an expert in creating and training bionic mechanical pets. Making these little things behave like real creatures with genuine desires and self-awareness is quite challenging - tasks artificial intelligence cannot accomplish, as simulated consciousness can only replicate simulations, not comprehend the desires behind them. \n\nPerfectly dosed flaws and logical paradoxes allow each biomechanical pet [PAWN_pronoun] trains to develop vivid and utterly unique personalities. Yet [PAWN_pronoun] never doubts whether these machines possess true life.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>5</Crafting>
			<Animals>4</Animals>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Social>-4</Social>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space33</defName>
		<title>celestia post-modern artist</title>
		<titleShort>neo-artist</titleShort>
		<description>Not all art attracts admiration, and [PAWN_nameDef]'s work exemplifies this. Sometimes people perceive [PAWN_possessive] designs as random combinations from a chaotic lexicon, yet pieces like "Countless Yaks Gazing Beyond the Sculpture, Symbolizing Chaos" occasionally evoke inexplicable awe, radiating transcendent beauty.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>7</Artistic>
			<Social>3</Social>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Mining>-5</Mining>
			<Plants>-2</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space34</defName>
		<title>celestia couturier</title>
		<titleShort>couturier</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s artistic flair drives [PAWN_pronoun] to design elegant fashion for fellow Celestia. To fully realize [PAWN_possessive] visions, [PAWN_pronoun] naturally mastered garment tailoring - aided by nanomachines. [PAWN_possessive] talent soon attracted custom orders from many, including Celestia officials. Rumor has it [PAWN_pronoun] contributed to the latest official uniform design.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>6</Artistic>
			<Crafting>4</Crafting>
			<Social>2</Social>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space35</defName>
		<title>celestia mechatronics designer</title>
		<titleShort>cyber-architect</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s mind constantly generates mechanical concepts, and Celestia's neural-link technology with nanomachines allows [PAWN_pronoun] to project these structures into reality. [PAWN_pronoun] has designed numerous bionic mechanisms widely used in Celestia society, including cargo handlers still prevalent in spaceports.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>7</Crafting>
			<Intellectual>4</Intellectual>
			<Artistic>1</Artistic>
			<Social>-5</Social>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space36</defName>
		<title>celestia tech-regulator</title>
		<titleShort>risk-control</titleShort>
		<description>"Controlled technology, controlled risks."\n\n[PAWN_nameDef] served in the Celestia Technology Oversight Committee, a specialized agency directly under the Celestia government, dedicated to mitigating the projected risks of hazardous technologies. [PAWN_pronoun] must deeply comprehend diverse technologies and their applications—and excel at envisioning their darkest possibilities. After rigorous evaluation, [PAWN_pronoun] employs negotiation, contracts, litigation, or even forceful suppression to neutralize and regulate technologies with latent threats, ensuring their ethical deployment.\n\nCelestia's advancements have long held the power to obliterate their own civilization: programmable nanomachines, pseudo-sentient AI, radical genetic editing, neural-link interfaces, ubiquitous antimatter energy... Countless perilous innovations necessitated regulators like [PAWN_nameDef] to strangle disasters at their inception. They chase the storm, yet are chased by it in turn.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Intellectual>8</Intellectual>
			<Crafting>4</Crafting>
			<Social>3</Social>
			<Shooting>3</Shooting>
			<Artistic>-6</Artistic>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space37</defName>
		<title>celestia heretic cyberneticist</title>
		<titleShort>fleshsmith</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an imaginative cybernetics specialist, renowned for designing lifelike prosthetic systems and personally installing custom augmentations for clients deemed worthy.\n\nThis continued until [PAWN_pronoun] mastered the use of DustMech-aligned genetic editing to engineer synthetic tissues, fusing these bioengineered masses with [PAWN_possessive] bespoke prosthetics. As [PAWN_possessive] creativity surged, [PAWN_pronoun] flung open the gates to uncharted realms, eager to test these innovations on [PAWN_objective]—only for the Technology Oversight Committee to storm into [PAWN_possessive] lab and slam those gates shut.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>6</Crafting>
			<Medicine>5</Medicine>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Social>-6</Social>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space38</defName>
		<title>celestia holovideographer</title>
		<titleShort>holoartist</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a new-era visual artist who uses neural-linked camera drones to create hyperrealistic holograms. [PAWN_pronoun] weaves emotional triggers into [PAWN_possessive] works, allowing viewers to relive memories with multisensory immersion. Patrons flock to [PAWN_objective] to eternally preserve their most precious moments.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>7</Artistic>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Social>2</Social>
			<Mining>-5</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space39</defName>
		<title>celestia virtuo-reality architect</title>
		<titleShort>virtuogenius</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] crafts immersive virtual worlds that cleverly bypass Celestia's reality-awareness laws. [PAWN_possessive] masterpiece 'The Fifth Expedition' lets players unravel cosmic mysteries while battling extradimensional horrors, blending narrative depth with meta-reality subversion.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>6</Artistic>
			<Intellectual>5</Intellectual>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Construction>-3</Construction>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space40</defName>
		<title>celestia neural-hedonist</title>
		<titleShort>taboo-designer</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] specializes in illicit VR experiences that bypass biological limitations. To perfect [PAWN_possessive] signature 'Transspecies Symphony' series, [PAWN_pronoun] personally tests neural-stimulation patterns in [PAWN_possessive] underground lab, blending scientific rigor with deviant creativity.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Artistic>5</Artistic>
			<Medicine>4</Medicine>
			<Animals>3</Animals>
			<Social>-6</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space41</defName>
		<title>celestia neurosurgeon</title>
		<titleShort>brainmender</titleShort>
		<description>After nanomechs restored [PAWN_nameDef]'s tremor-ridden hands, [PAWN_pronoun] developed psionic-assisted surgery techniques. Now [PAWN_pronoun] performs 27-hour neurografts with psychic precision, [PAWN_possessive] consciousness split between surgical drones and [PAWN_possessive] augmented body.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Medicine>8</Medicine>
			<Intellectual>4</Intellectual>
			<Social>-6</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space42</defName>
		<title>celestia clinic physician</title>
		<titleShort>frontier-doctor</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] operates a small clinic in an Outer Rim space habitation station. Managing government-issued nanomed units, [PAWN_pronoun] combats zero-gravity osteopenia and gunshot wounds alike. [PAWN_possessive] presence alone deters would-be troublemakers, making the clinic an oasis in the lawless void.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Medicine>5</Medicine>
			<Social>3</Social>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Mining>-3</Mining>
			<Construction>-2</Construction>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space43</defName>
		<title>celestia freighter captain</title>
		<titleShort>captain</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] commands a massive cargo hauler, sustaining civilization through interstellar trade. While secretly battling stress-induced insomnia, [PAWN_pronoun] maintains calm authority during 30-lightyear voyages, coordinating shipments like a cosmic conductor.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>5</Social>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Plants>-3</Plants>
			<Mining>-2</Mining>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space44</defName>
		<title>celestia freighter captain</title>
		<titleShort>captain</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s obsession with shipboard micromanagement borders on madness. Every airscrubber efficiency report feeds [PAWN_possessive] tyrannical control, yet beneath the ruthless exterior lies desperate hope to deliver [PAWN_possessive] crew safely home.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Intellectual>6</Intellectual>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Medicine>-3</Medicine>
			<Animals>-3</Animals>
			<Social>-2</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space45</defName>
		<title>celestia compassionate volunteer</title>
		<titleShort>goodsamaritan</titleShort>
		<description>Beyond [PAWN_possessive] primary duties, [PAWN_nameDef] selflessly aids others across hospitals and spaceports. While AI could handle these tasks, [PAWN_pronoun] believes genuine human warmth - a smile, a kind word - makes all the difference in the cold void of space.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>4</Social>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Cooking>2</Cooking>
			<Mining>-3</Mining>
			<Shooting>-2</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space46</defName>
		<title>celestia community delegate</title>
		<titleShort>spokesperson</titleShort>
		<description>Elected by [PAWN_possessive] neighbors, [PAWN_nameDef] voices community concerns in stellar assemblies. Though sometimes stumbling through complex policy debates, [PAWN_pronoun]'s earnest efforts to balance diverse interests are gradually gaining recognition across the system.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>6</Social>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Artistic>2</Artistic>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Plants>-2</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space47</defName>
		<title>celestia antimatter engineer</title>
		<titleShort>corekeeper</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] maintains the beating heart of a space habitat - a magnetic containment antimatter reactor. While micromachines handle daily operations, [PAWN_pronoun]'s expertise in calibrating energy output curves ensures the station never flickers.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>6</Crafting>
			<Intellectual>4</Intellectual>
			<Construction>2</Construction>
			<Social>-5</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space48</defName>
		<title>celestia stellar-ring engineer</title>
		<titleShort>ringbuilder</titleShort>
		<description>Overseeing a segment of the colossal solar particle accelerator, [PAWN_nameDef] converts stellar plasma into usable matter/antimatter pairs. [PAWN_possessive] daily calibrations of the 0.97c particle streams fuel entire star systems.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Construction>8</Construction>
			<Intellectual>6</Intellectual>
			<Mining>2</Mining>
			<Social>-4</Social>
			<Plants>-3</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space49</defName>
		<title>celestia stellar-tech delegate</title>
		<titleShort>technocrat</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] wields considerable influence on Celestia's Central Committee as a technological representative. With [PAWN_possessive] eloquence and profound understanding of socio-technological systems, [PAWN_pronoun] helps shape civilization's future through key policy decisions.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>6</Social>
			<Intellectual>5</Intellectual>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space50</defName>
		<title>celestia navigator architect</title>
		<titleShort>ark-designer</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] participated in the critical design and planning of a key component of "The Navigator Programme." This initiative, serving as the ultimate contingency plan, aims to dispatch Celestia's embers to distant star systems before the inevitable and total collapse of the "BlueFlood." The light-speed barrier will forever constrain these exiled voyagers from returning home, rendering this journey a one-way odyssey for most. After the embers depart, the guardians of the home star system will attempt to obliterate the source of all calamities.\n\nNow, [PAWN_nameDef] voyages with "The Navigator Programme," awakening only sporadically during the endless journey. While maintaining the ark-ship's cryogenic hibernation systems, [PAWN_pronoun] also serves as a chronicler, documenting the indelible epic of Celestia's civilization.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Intellectual>7</Intellectual>
			<Construction>6</Construction>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Social>-5</Social>
			<Animals>-2</Animals>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space51</defName>
		<title>celestia abyssia caretaker</title>
		<titleShort>caretaker</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] entered into a long-term service agreement with an Abyssia. Barring unforeseen circumstances, [PAWN_pronoun] would have dutifully served as a steward until retirement.\n\nThe Abyssia—creators of the Celestia, pioneers of the homeworld, and the original Celestia themselves—grow increasingly frail due to their ill-adaptedness to the space environment. The cognitive patterns of the earliest Abyssia have already entered a millennia-long decline. As part of a form of elder care and end-of-life support, [PAWN_nameDef] spent decades striving to fulfill the employer’s physiological and psychological needs.\n\nYet "The Navigator Programme" became that unforeseen circumstance. Stranded in deep space, tens or hundreds of light-years from [PAWN_possessive] charge, it leaves [PAWN_objective] perpetually entangled by unresolved obligations.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Medicine>6</Medicine>
			<Social>6</Social>
			<Cooking>6</Cooking>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Shooting>-3</Shooting>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space52</defName>
		<title>Celestia Marine Infantry</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an ordinary member of the Celestia Navy, commanding an automated assault squad. By directing autonomous machines to breach enemy lines alongside [PAWN_pronoun], Celestia steadily reclaimed territory from mechanoids and insectoids. Each time [PAWN_pronoun] was injured, Celestia's medical technology healed [PAWN_pronoun], allowing [PAWN_pronoun] to return to the war with more experience, gradually making [PAWN_pronoun] fearless in the face of death.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>5</Shooting>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Melee>2</Melee>
			<Social>-4</Social>
			<Animals>-2</Animals>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space53</defName>
		<title>Celestia Marine Infantry</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] enlisted and became an ordinary member of the Celestia Marine Corps, fighting on the front lines against mechanoids.\n\nAs [PAWN_pronoun] moved from one star system to another, [PAWN_nameDef] gradually realized that no amount of enemies slain would change [PAWN_possessive] life. [PAWN_pronoun] began focusing on saving others—rescuing comrades whose bodies were not yet brain-dead, at least saving their lives this once.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Medicine>6</Medicine>
			<Shooting>4</Shooting>
			<Social>2</Social>
			<Construction>-3</Construction>
			<Mining>-2</Mining>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space54</defName>
		<title>Celestia Marine Infantry</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] served in the Celestia Marine Corps. Celestia's advancements in mechanoid control greatly enhanced soldiers' combat capabilities, and [PAWN_nameDef] excelled at maximizing this technology. With [PAWN_possessive] flexible tactical thinking, [PAWN_pronoun] often achieved unexpected combat results using just a few mechanoids, earning [PAWN_pronoun] the occasional nickname "the fox" from [PAWN_possessive] teammates.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Crafting>5</Crafting>
			<Shooting>4</Shooting>
			<Intellectual>3</Intellectual>
			<Social>-4</Social>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space55</defName>
		<title>Celestia Marine Infantry</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<description>It’s awkward to admit, but [PAWN_nameDef] joined the military partly for the sake of a steady meal. However, when faced with the roar of artillery and the bloodshed of battle, [PAWN_pronoun] found there was no turning back.\n\nOnce, a group of mechanoids breached the defenses and nearly detected [PAWN_pronoun] through the data stream, despite [PAWN_possessive] crude camouflage. A bullet pierced [PAWN_possessive] body. When [PAWN_pronoun] awoke with these memories, [PAWN_pronoun] found [PAWN_reflective] in a medical bay, having narrowly escaped death. [PAWN_nameDef] suddenly realized that the war [PAWN_pronoun] was fighting was no virtual reality game.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>4</Shooting>
			<Melee>4</Melee>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Artistic>-4</Artistic>
			<Animals>-3</Animals>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space56</defName>
		<title>Celestia Veteran</title>
		<titleShort>Veteran</titleShort>
		<description>After enduring many trials, [PAWN_nameDef] retired from the Celestia Marine Corps with honors and gleaming medals.\n\nEven though [PAWN_pronoun] survived the smoke-filled, blood-soaked battlefields, and even though Celestia's technology could repair all physical injuries and disabilities, the prolonged stress of fighting mechanoids left [PAWN_pronoun] restless and haunted by nightmares. With the help of the Naval Veterans Affairs Department, [PAWN_pronoun] secured a new job and life—a leisurely position and a chance to heal both body and mind.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>6</Shooting>
			<Melee>4</Melee>
			<Medicine>2</Medicine>
			<Social>-5</Social>
			<Intellectual>-1</Intellectual>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space57</defName>
		<title>Celestia Marine Special Forces</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a member of the Orbital Drop Shock Troopers, one of the most elite marine units in the Celestia Navy. Unlike other forces that deploy via landing craft or aerospace vehicles, [PAWN_pronoun] descended in advanced orbital drop pods at supersonic speeds, carrying firepower足以 to neutralize even a destroyer. [PAWN_pronoun] struck deep behind enemy lines, eliminating anti-orbital weapons before launching assaults and clearing the area for subsequent operations. A wave of military machinery and high-energy explosives would then engulf the enemy positions.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>6</Shooting>
			<Melee>4</Melee>
			<Construction>2</Construction>
			<Social>-5</Social>
			<Animals>-3</Animals>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space58</defName>
		<title>Celestia Cruiser Artillery</title>
		<titleShort>Artillery</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as an artillery operator aboard a Celestia cruiser, directing high-energy self-contained plasma and energy torrents toward the enemies of Celestia. [PAWN_pronoun] also mastered a range of mechanical and information technologies, taking on the task of maintaining these instruments of war when necessary.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Shooting>5</Shooting>
			<Crafting>3</Crafting>
			<Intellectual>2</Intellectual>
			<Social>-4</Social>
			<Plants>-2</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space59</defName>
		<title>Celestia Cruiser Captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] was the captain of a Celestia cruiser, renowned for [PAWN_possessive] aggressive and offensive tactics. [PAWN_possessive] combat style and professional expertise often led the command to assign [PAWN_pronoun] various assault missions. With [PAWN_possessive] exceptional command skills, [PAWN_pronoun] repeatedly spearheaded into the heart of enemy forces, delivering致命 strikes and retreating unscathed.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Intellectual>6</Intellectual>
			<Social>4</Social>
			<Shooting>3</Shooting>
			<Mining>-5</Mining>
			<Plants>-3</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space60</defName>
		<title>Celestia Stellar Military Representative</title>
		<titleShort>Representative</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] has endured countless battles and studied numerous ancient and modern military strategies. Soon after, [PAWN_pronoun] was chosen to represent the military's interests in the Central Committee, providing expert military advice and analysis to the committee, while striving to secure better conditions for the soldiers.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<requiredWorkTags>
			<li>Violent</li>
		</requiredWorkTags>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>6</Social>
			<Intellectual>4</Intellectual>
			<Shooting>2</Shooting>
			<Crafting>-4</Crafting>
			<Mining>-2</Mining>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

	<AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef ParentName="Celes_BaseAdultBackstory">
		<defName>Celes_Backstory_Space61</defName>
		<title>celestia teacher</title>
		<titleShort>teacher</titleShort>
		<description>[PAWN_nameDef] teaches at a school. The foundational knowledge that once required over a decade of learning no longer needs to be taught step-by-step by instructors. Instead, [PAWN_nameDef]'s role as a teacher is to answer questions, resolve doubts, and guide students on how to apply knowledge and how to explore and discover. Practice is the only true method of mastering knowledge.</description>
		<slot>Adulthood</slot>
		<skillGains>
			<Social>5</Social>
			<Intellectual>4</Intellectual>
			<Artistic>2</Artistic>
			<Mining>-4</Mining>
			<Plants>-3</Plants>
		</skillGains>
		<spawnCategories>
			<li>Celes_Space</li>
		</spawnCategories>
	</AlienRace.AlienBackstoryDef>

</Defs>